negative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
mmm
hmm
herbs
n
tee
Hm
mmm
ENDINGS
Let's go from the beginning.
Please.
The doors have opened.
Come out, Mr. Sound.
First song.
Like this.
Hello!
Hello! Hi, everyone!
Hi!
Wow!
No!
Oh, no!
It's starting.
Hey, guys.
What's going on? This one right here.
What's going on right now?
About 200 people.
200 people are watching this?
Thank you very much.
For being here today.
So many roommates.
What are you doing here?
What did they come for?
Did you come to see me?
Today.
You, don't talk too much, or I'll sing right away.You, don't talk too much or we'll start singing right away.
A song?
A song. We're going to sing a song.
We'll sing a song.
On time, on time, on time.
On time, on time, on time, on time.
Wait a minute.
You're going to sing right after the show?
Yes, sir.
Yuzuki's FF2023... and then suddenly you're singing?
I think I'm singing.
I'm sure you won't get applause like you did before.
Because it's uninhabited.
And I'm in the silence.
Are you going to sing alone?
I'm going to sing.
Yes, I'm going to have some fun.
No one's watching.
What are you looking forward to?
I'm excited.
Singing.
Singing and dancing.
Dancing is a bit of an exaggeration.
I'll sing.
Please invite your son!
Next announcement, Shunsuke Setoguchi is here!
Hello!
Dear father, please.
Dear Sir?
Maybe I'll be worshipped.
Hold the microphone.
Hold the mike.
It's okay. Yes, sir.
So I'm going to sing something, too, as usual.
I hope we can start singing soon.
I don't think it's going so well, to be honest, but 300 people showed up for the first part of the show.
Okay, and then for the first part...
Then the first part is to introduce the members of the Setoguchi Atsugumi Association.
Yes, I sang a selected song.
Two selected. Another one selected.
Then Ogawa from Scrap!
He's coming out now.
Ogawa-kun
Ogawa-kun of Ogawa-kun
Yes, and you two sing together.
I understand.
We've already decided on a title for the song.
Yes, we have.
Yes...
Ogawa-kun, you can throw up.
Ogawa-san, you can!
And...
Set Gucci's first union, Leaver.
Lieber.
Diva!
Oh Deeber?
Yes, ma'am.
All right, let me introduce you to Set Gucci's first union, Deaver.
Deaver Yuzuki!
Hi.
He just came out like that.
But is it a solo?
No, it's not.
We were selected here, too.
We're the two chosen for the song.
What are they going to sing?
They're going to sing something.
Shall we sing a song this morning?
Yes.
Not "yes". What are you going to sing? Okay, yes.
Here we go.
Now it's time to say goodbye Let's fly away, trusting in the light
Believe in the power of youth
Oh!
It's like a Neptune comedy.
What's this? Horikensasu?
I was so surprised, but they're going to sing something.
I see... two people singing... I see... and...
And with that, the audience went...
Tenko!
They're all out!
You've been here so many times... and you do it every time?
Is it Atsumiya Setoguchi?
Whose Tenko?
No, the director.
There's no such thing.
If I had said so, you would have panicked.
Yes, there is no such thing.
Yes, sir.
After this, we'll be introduced.
Here we go.
It's 1:55 p.m. in Mass.
The opening arc is at 1:55 p.m.
I see. Let's introduce them.
Let's go in there and introduce Nutto, our research student.
So we're going to see the research student Nutto?
Nut? So we're just going to finish this episode?
I see. I'm sure we'll have plenty of time.
It's 2:00 p.m. sharp.It's exactly 2:00 p.m.
I see. We have about five minutes before it starts.
For various reasons.
Okay, then. Thank you very much. I'll tell them it'll be starting soon.
And when I call, there's a five-minute delay, and then something like "Hatsu-chu-i" comes on.
No, it's not the same thing. It's definitely not the same day.
It's a hair call.
Is that right? Then you're right.
Here it comes.
I see.
The second part is a little different.
The second part is different?
Yes... first, Setoguchi's father.
Can you tell me the time? The venue?
5:45 p.m.
Setoguchi's father.
Yes, sir.
So are you going to sing a different song again?
Yes, I will sing a different song.
For whom?
For everyone's amusement.
They're all gone.
Who are you singing for?
And you, Mr. Setoguchi?
Yes, yes, yes.
What's this?
A duet by Mr. Setoguchi and his father.
Father and son together.
I see.
And the next one...
Yes.
Can I go?
Yes, you may.
Setoguchi Atsuhisa Mime's Diva
What?
What? Karaoke is available.
No, no, no, you didn't mean no singing, right? Yes, yes!
Straight up? Well, it's not a full-length show, is it?
I see. So they're going to do it all over the place?
Diva? If it's inside the venue, it's fine.
Around 6:10 p.m., I think.
Mr. Knight.
So you're going to do it at 6:10 p.m.? By one more person.
And? It would be better if Mr. Omuro and Mr. Setoguchi were there then.
I see... I see.
So Yuzuki will appear with Rumpin?
So two Diva members will appear.
Rumpin' Rumpin'.
Wow.
Then let's stay much closer to Mr. Naito.
Liuer is so dorky.
Is this how you do it?
Call me by 6:25 p.m.
We don't have much time left.
You're not going to talk until 6:25 p.m., are you?
But you can come back a little earlier. Take five minutes.
Okay.
I understand.
The whole hall will be there, including the fake dad, Ogawa-san, Daikoku-san, and Naito-san, who'll appear again on his own.
I see. I see. Gorgeous. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry it's not a game.
I'm sorry, it's not a game. I'm just saying I haven't seen it either.
I'm sorry, I didn't see the game.
Don't worry. Don't worry. I was a little zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz.
So we're going to do it at Setoguchi's birthday party.
After the first and second parts of Yuzuki's FF, we'll be at Tokyo Mystery Circus on the first floor.
On that day, there will be a limited edition of goods for sale at the I LOVE SHUNSUKE SHOP to celebrate Setoguchi's birthday.
T-shirts and stickers are designed by Shunsuke Mizukami.
As I mentioned, we were going to sell Mr. Mizukami's noodle, and it seems to have been completed.
Today, five of them brought the actual products.
Please take a look at the center.
Can you see them?
You can already see them!
Mr. Mizukami! Too late, too late!
So, Mr. Mizukami brought us this.
Mr. Mizukami's mask!
Well, Mr. Nai-nai-san, Mr. Ru-Nai-nai-san...
It's a mask that everyone can make into Ms. Mizukami by using their power.
May I make the presentation?
Yes, this way, please.
I'm scared!
You're selling these! And they're handmade!
Seriously, everyone!
It's 500 yen a piece.
I thought it was a bad idea to film it.
[Comment] It's 500 yen for 1 card, and 1000 yen for 3 cards.
[Comment] You get a good deal on one. [Comment] Please buy it with the expensive one.
Oh, I see. So, 500 yen for 1 piece, 1000 yen for 3 pieces, I see.
I see. So, let's all get together and buy three T-shirts at once for the best price.
Ah, Shunsuke Setoguchi's, yes, yes [Comment] 3,800 yen.
That's too expensive! That's too expensive! It won't sell!
Still, it's a big deal. How many are you limited to? Fifty-three.
I've never heard of such an order. 53 pieces? Fifty-three pieces.
Limited to 53 pieces? Will it sell? I wonder if they'll sell. - Comment: 44 pieces of projector bookies.
You better not say too much. You better not say too much. Those 44 are the lowest, and they ain't coming back at all.
What's the percentage of sales, man? If you don't sell 44, you can't even break even?
And you only sold 53. That's not much profit! Seriously, how much for the stickers? Stickers.
Three sets of three. Oh, three sets of three. Well, there were three different colors.Comment] Set of 3. Oh, set of 3.
Comment] 1,000 yen.
How many are there? How many stickers did you order? 90 sets.
Wow, you're aggressive with the stickers.
Almost only stickers are sold! Okay, so that's how many we'll be selling.
What about the stickers? That's a good point.
Oh, really? Yes. What time do you start selling them? From what time?
You're going to sell them near Tokyo Mystery Circus, right? At first, around 11:00, 11:00.
So the goods you just mentioned will be available at ZEPP Shinjuku and Tokyo Mystery Circus from 11:00 a.m.? That's right.
I see... [Comment] It was a bit rainy then, wasn't it?
[Comment] Originally, I was going to sell it on the soil on my own, but it's no good.
I was originally going to sell it on its own in the soil, but I thought it needed a roof.
I think it's going to be under a roof somewhere in Mystery Circus.
I think it's going to be under a roof somewhere in the Mystery Circus.
I think it's going to be under some roof at the Mystery Circus...
Wait a minute, you're going to sell it inside Mystery Circus?
I don't think so.
Please do not contact Mystery Circus at all!
I'm so scared...
Please don't ask the Mystery Circus staff on the day of the event where they sell the tickets. I don't know.
I understand.
Not at all.
You have to look for it in the atmosphere.
Please be adventurous and buy a few things.
please.
So, that's it.
3,800 yen is too much.
What do you think? Mr. Mizukan.
I think it's totally fine.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I see.
Well, here we go.
We've got the championship ballot.
I've got some rehearsal work to do.
I don't know what I have to do.
I don't know. Do you have a full-length version of what you're going to do?
Oh! That's it? Enjoy life, right?
I see. We were talking about making it a regular event, like a yuzuki.
It would be nice if we could do it at the beginning and at the end.
Enjoy Life this time, too.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mr. Satoguchi, do you remember the choreography?
I don't remember any of them.
There was one like this, wasn't there? What's that?
There it is! There was this one, wasn't there?
I have an image that I really liked this part, but I don't remember it at all.
Then, where do you want to go from here?
We're going with this flow, aren't we?
We will rehearse.
Then, please memorize it, Mr. Roumays.
Is it the chorus?
Where do you dance from and to?
I'm a member, so I'd like you to dance the full thing, though.
No, no, we're all going to do it together.
You're going to have as many different people as possible.
So they will be there. Mizukami-san is definitely going to be there.
There's also Nise Papa.
Mizukami-san, you're looking at the comment section all the time.
Remembering the play with Ms. Mizukami.
Remember.
We did it until the day before. Remember? Mizukami-san.
We practiced so much.
I'm talking to him. I've been ignoring you.
I think I've memorized it.
Really? I'm sorry. I don't want to have a fake father.
Among the male members, Ogawa-san is the best.
I see that Ogawa-san is not here today.
Mr. Ogawa is supposed to be there, too.
Only a part of the show. He is supposed to be in only part of the show.
For some reason, he can't appear in the second part.
I'm only going to be there for part of the show.
I don't know what to do. I can go and stir things up because I can speak up.
I see.
Just make sure you go and figure out where that call is.
There's a lot to remember.
I don't want to.
That's fine. Let's just do it.
First of all, let's relearn how to pretend.
It's your first time, isn't it?
I look forward to working with you.
It is a precious time for me to learn from you, Mr. Ogawa.
Please teach us.
Where should we start?
Let's start from the beginning!
Then, please put your weight on either the right or left side!
And!
I remember we had some kind of formation!
Then, then, then, then, then!
Oh, yeah!
Setoguchi-san, you start playing first there!
No!
Why!
I can't remember!
Let's be Mr. Mizukami or something!
That's too much! It's totally fine!
So it's okay if you start playing the guitar, Mr. Mizukami?
Is it OK if Mr. Mizukami starts playing the guitar?
We'll play in order, right?
Please do.
Here it is.This is it.
It's uninhabited.
I don't know where it is.
No, it's not.
Enjoy life.
Enjoy your life.
I'm going to save this stuff.
I'm saving this stuff.
What's that? That's a problem letter.
I'm sorry. I'll do it right.
That's right.
Let's go here.
Let's go to the street.
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm going to start shouting out.
The intro is going to be oi.
I'm going to go in with a shisso.
I'm just going to pause two.
What was that?
Shissou, tsutsukutsukutsu to the contract.
Hotto, and then two.
Four. Four in total.
Make it four.
I see. I guess not.
Whatever.
I was free.
But please do it in pieces.
I'm going.
Shush, and be modest in your contract.
Hot, so two pieces.
They're all in order there, aren't they?
What's with the alignment there?
Do the voices naturally come together?
Do it again.
Shush.
No, no, no, it's just the two of us.
Mizukami-san, why are you trying to match your fake dad?
I want to see the original.
I want to see it.
I'll go. Ready.
Is that it, Papa?
That's right. It's Sparta.
Ready. Shissou.
So that's the first one?
That's right. After "Sissou".
I see. I see.
Fake Dad, why don't you do it the other way around?
Reverse?
Yes, the other way around. I'll stretch it out.
Oh, okay, okay. So, I did it.
And it's been a long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long.
I'm satisfied. Left. Oh! I remember!
It goes on. That's good, too.
Yes, yes. That's how it was.
Is it okay? No, it's not.
Two steps, then up, and then we'll do the "Kururimpa.
You stretched with the Kururimpa. I stretched.
And now, "Ehen".
Oh, that's ahem. It's going to be ahem.
Is that okay?
That's good, too. A little more. Just a little more.
There are things I want to do a little more, and I don't want to put up with it.
I said, "I don't want to put up with it," and this is what I got from Mr. Senda.
You did it once or twice, didn't you?
Are you doing well?
Are you doing well? Are you getting there?
I see. No, you just keep going and going.
Okay, let's do it one time, one way. Let's do this one time, one way.
You can look at the archives later and memorize it.
Okay. Teacher.
Then it will be B-melody.
It's Nobita again.
What's this song?
It's difficult, isn't it?
It's difficult.
×I'm sure it's difficult.
Adults say it's absolutely impossible.
Danjan!
That's not true... you'll fall down from Setoguchi-san.
Oh, that's right.
That's not true.
Oh, yeah, yeah
Feels good.
Like this, Setoguchi-san.
That's how you put your hips in.
Shall we?
I remember last year.
The freest guy in the world...
Chi-chi-tagoo group
And you're free until the end of the chorus.
Yes, sir.
Hachi group
Here we go!
Enjoy!
Please raise your hands
Enjoy life dispatch school
Don't fall in love with me, don't fall in love, don't fall in love, don't fall in love
Today and tomorrow morning
This leg is because it's hard
It's because it's hardIt's because it's hard.
When I go this way...
I turn this leg this way.
Close.
When you go this way, turn this foot this way.
That's it. That's all you have to do.
Today, tomorrow, even if it's in the morning
Oh, I'm so light!
I'm so light!
Mr. Ohu.
I like it.
It's nice to be light.
It's like that.
But enjoy it here.
Today, tomorrow, even if it's in the morning...
I don't know.
Then it depends on the formation.
Let's start with the one on the left.
Let's dance.
The one on the right.
Let's dance a second time.
Let's all dance together.
Let's dance!
Gggh!
Good job!
Let's do it!
I'm not afraid of the flames
I'm not afraid.
You gotta try it.
we can't start now.
It's big.
I'm dreaming.
And then, now that we're here, the two of us, the two in the middle, let's make some noise.
Let's make noise. Then the two at the end shout from the inside to the outside.
Then the two of us here will skip.
Let's skip. And then we'll all go, ready to go!
We have not played enough yet.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Here we go. All of them.
Impossible.
Daikoku-san, it's absolutely impossible in the middle of the delivery. To be honest, I don't recognize this red dress.
I'm sure I'll recognize you from past videos.
Then, let's finish up at the top.
I see.
The chorus is the same.
I know, right? That's still the creepy part. We can do it together.
Also, Enjoy Life has a lot of intros and outros.
In the A melody, there is a chord that calls Naochan or Haru-chan at the end of the singer,
The B melody is
So, I hope my roommates will learn that too.
Yes, I'll leave the calling to the roommates.
Yes, I want to be the first one to call out at the Hair Fest in September.
I'd love to be there.
Yes, I want to.
I've been doing this for two years, two years now.
Somewhere, somewhere, I want to have a Spring/Spring/March type of performance.
Yes, I do.
Then let's make that place too.
Yes, that place too.
Isn't it too long? Shunsuke.
Shun-chan?
That's not good.
Heh heh heh, that's bad.
Setogu
Setogu!
What part? Can you say "Setogu"?
What's good?
It's good, it's good. If there's something you want.
I'll leave it to you.
Let's each call Shunsuke by his name.
You say "formation".
How many people are in it?
The first and the last.
I'd like to see everyone as much as possible.
They're all here.
I see.
So, in the end...
I don't think we'll be dancing after all.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
You know...
I think so too
I wonder...
What if Mr. Vachon...
I don't know about that.
If he comes out, will he be able to dance the basic parts?
I think so.
Yes, I think so.
When you dance, everyone is there.
When you dance, everyone is there, so it's like a "yay" with everyone.
It creates a good atmosphere, doesn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I just realized it might happen.
I just realized it, didn't I?
That's right!
Only Daikoku-san sang well last time.Only Daikoku-san sang well the other night.
Let's just do this one.
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it!
Enjoy life at the dispatch school.
That's right.
Don't you mean you'll do it? That's right, let's do it. It would be pleasant if we could do it together.
I'll give you a lecture on that part. Please do. Right hand, right hand.
Enjoy raising your hands! If you go beyond the life dispatch school, you'll only have to do Punch Dong and Koi Harang Bang Jong.
I see. I see. Suddenly. No, it's fine. How about you, Ms. Mizukami? Yes.
You think you can do it? It's fun, isn't it? Mizukami-san, we actually did it last year, and fun is fun, isn't it?
It's just that we are a little out of our depth. No, no, no. And Ogawa-kun is there. He probably danced a lot. At the end, only one of them was dancing fully.
Faithfully. Mr. Ogawa sang faithfully. He was faithful. I don't know about the guests. They came out with cardboard boxes and disinfectant.
I don't think they could do anything but dance. I heard that they were told to bring something with them. There was a story going around that you had to bring something with you to get out. Everyone came out with a hair dryer or a box of tissues.
So let's let them know that we want to do it here this time. Yes, that's right. Let's do it here. Let's do it here.
It's good, isn't it?
In the chorus, this appears twice in one chorus,
The second chorus is this one, and the last chorus is this one, too.
I think I can manage the chorus. Please remember it.
Thank you very much.
I remembered it last year. Daikoku-san taught me how to do it, and we did it for a few hours. Before delivery.
We did it. It was a valuable experience.
You're not in the mood for it?
Don't you like to dance? Do you like it?
I can't dance at all.
Really? Let's practice a little. Even if it's just the chorus.
I remember a lot of things. I remember that.
I'm sure Petit dances with Chloe and others.
I can't do it anymore. Stop saying unnecessary things.
I can't do it anymore. I can't do it anymore.
Chloe is quite difficult.
Takuya made my part much easier, so I was able to do it.
You also did Rocket Queen, didn't you?
Yes, I did. I really did.
But we also did Rainbow the other day.
Rainbow can do the two-person motorcycle part.
That's right. Right here.
I can do it.
I can do it. I can do it.
I don't know if it's on the set list or not.
I don't know if it's on the program or not, but I don't know.
I don't know if it's on the program or not, but I don't know if it's on the program.
It will be held at Rep Shinjuku. There will be two parts.
There are still a few tickets available.
A few more. There are still a few tickets left.
I hope you will come to the event if you would like to attend.
So, this was an open rehearsal. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Please look forward to seeing you at the show.
Great. Shall we sit here?
Shall we?
You're strangers now.
We happen to be a family.
We were in front of and behind each other.
So... what do you think?
How's the fun?
I've already decided.
Really?
I just decided the other day.
The first and second parts are completely different.
Really?
Well, we're looking into it, but right now we're not sure.
By all means.
Please tell me with your facial expressions.
The performers for the first and second parts are different, aren't they?
So I'm thinking of making the set list to match the performers.
I made it like this.
So I made it like this.
Let's see...
Uh...
What's it like to match the performers? There are quite a few songs.
And one of the features of Yuzuki's Air Fest is that each group performs for quite a while.
Each group performs for quite a long time at Yuzuki Air Fest.
We also have a lot of different kinds of music.
A lot of songs? Yes, a lot. That's good.
We play a lot of songs.
Some of them are...
They're hot.
Oh, that's nice.
The second part is hot, but cool.
Oh, I see.
The second part is cool because of the cool shirts.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And then...
We'll be performing some new songs that we've been working on for the free live tour, and some songs that we haven't performed in a while.
Oh, you don't know about the other groups yet? You don't know? No, I don't.
I see. I'm looking forward to it. The first time, Mr. Bashio did a lot of what Daikoku requested.
We didn't talk about that this time. I'm sure each group will show us the best they have to offer.
I'm sure each group will show us the best performance they can give us right now, so please come. I'm really looking forward to it.
I've been watching the weather forecast every day, and it's raining.
It's supposed to thunder today. It's supposed to rain.
But I heard that the forecast was for rain on the 30th and 31st, but it turned out to be fine.
That's right. So it looks like it's going to happen.
Daikoku-san has the power of words.
Daikoku, is it a genie?
Daikoku-san, it's a genie? Yes, it's a spirit of words. That's why I'm feeling better.
I'm hoping for a miracle in Yusuki's room.
It's inside the room, so it's fine inside... but...
I'm sure there will be groups of people waiting outside.
And it's a crowded place in the city, so it's a little tough when it's raining, isn't it?
Yes, yes... please be careful.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm getting a little nervous.I'm getting nervous.
I don't know. Nervous?
I don't know if I'm nervous or what, but I'm not sure if I'll be okay.
They made me record the karaoke today.
You did it yourself?
Yes, I did it for all of them.
I don't think so.
I'm doing something that we can do together.
I'm wondering if it's something like "fake dad" or "yes, yes" or something like that.
We are duet singers too, right?
Why did you choose that song?
It's a song that holds a lot of memories for me.
It's not a memory at all.
It's a memory for me.
It's a memory for you? I understand.
So that's it.
Well... he comes to me through Mr. T.
He comes on the line with Mr. T in between.
He would ask me, "I would like you to do this job, too, Mr. Setoguchi.
You can't refuse.
You can't say no. They want you to do it.
They would say, "Do it.
If you put on the water omen, now you get the "kami-peron" sound.
So it's like that.
We will sell it, please.
I wonder how it will turn out. I'm looking forward to it.
I am looking forward to it.
I know you just commented on it, but it was certainly the first time too.
As I recall, the weather was bad in the morning. The weather was bad in the morning at Shin-Kiba.
The first time. Oh, that's right.
That's right. After that, it cleared up quite a bit.
Yes, it did.
Last year it was fine, but last year it rained a lot on the way back.
Was it?
So Mr. Mizukami got lost, and I arrived home at 2:00 a.m.
Oh, really? Was that right?
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes. That's why.
That's it. That's the Kawasaki place, right?
That's right. When we did it at Club Citta.
So it's already raining.
I'm sorry, but maybe.
I was calling for rain.
No, I was calling for rain.
I see.
Well, well, well... I'll let the power of words do the talking here.
Let's do something about it.
Well, I'd like to do something about that before we go outdoors.
This rainy tradition.
But let's get rid of it this time.
Rain is in the forecast for now, but if it clears up, we can do something about it,
If it clears up, as you say, it will clear up in the future when the event is held outdoors.
Yes, yes. Yes, for sure.
Let's go to the corner now. Okay. Okay, Ogura-san.
I mean, you haven't introduced yourself at all, and you haven't explained what this Yuzuki's Room is.
Who is it?
Who are you?
There might be.
I am Shunsuke Setoguchi, the administrator of Yuzuki's room. Please come in.
And I'm Yuuki Ogura, a member of the team. Please give me your best regards.
So, please tell us about the live delivery service called "Yuuki's Room," which also hosts festivals like this one.
Yes, every Monday from 9:00 p.m. on YouTube's Orca channel.
Setoguchi-san, a well-known scrapper of Real Dust Game, and Yuuki Ogura, a killer whale, sometimes welcome guests and talk about various topics.
Yes, that's right. If you are watching this program, we call you "roommates".
We also call you "roommates" if you are a fan of Team Orca, including Tahmin, so please join us for this hour.
If you would like to join us, please add the hashtag "Yuuki's room" and the URL of the streaming video.
Please do so.
Then, let's go to the corner of "Whenever you want. Ogura-san, please.
This week's Orca!
Good morning.
This is the corner where Mr. Ogura, a member of Team Shachi, will look back on the week himself.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sure you had a busy week, Mr. Ogura, how was it?
How was your week?
Oh, there are a lot of things I can't tell you.
What? You had the free release event live, but you also did a lot of other work?
Yes, I have a lot to look forward to. By the way, what kind of work is that, and what is the range of what you can say?
What kind? For example, filming?
Filming!
There is filming and there is recording. There's filming and there's recording.
I'm like, "Oh, I see! I see!
Is the release event on the weekend? Yes! I'm currently planning to release a 4-song EP called "Awaiting Bear" on June 28th.
I am releasing an EP called "Awaiting Bear" on June 28th, which contains 4 songs written by Kenta Matsuguma, and I am currently on a free live tour with it,
The day before yesterday was
The day before yesterday was a free live concert at a place called Akaike in Aichi Prefecture. The day before yesterday was a free live performance at a place called Akaike in Aichi Prefecture, and yesterday was a free live performance at Morinomiya Kizmall in Osaka.
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you very much.
I had an image that you would do weekend concerts in the same area, but this time you had to move from Nagoya to Osaka, didn't you?
Yes, we did.
How was it in your hometown of Aichi?
It was fun. As I may have mentioned before, there is a wide staircase at the back of the stage.
Both sides are aisles, but in the middle you can sit and watch the show.
So it's a little bit like a hall.
It's a little bit like a hall.
It's a good place for tough people to see the show.
And for us, it's a place where we can see the audience easily.
It's one of my favorite places.
It was a lot of fun.
How was the weather? Both of them.
The weather was hot.
So it was sunny? It was sunny.So it was sunny? It was fine.
I see. It's like Orca to do it in the heat, isn't it?
Yes, it was. But you were inside. Yes, it was fine.
It was fine, but it was very hot yesterday because we were outside.
It was very hot. Everyone was urging each other to stay hydrated.
Yesterday was my first time in Osaka in a long time. Is it the first time this year? The first time to do a live concert?
Yes, it is.
Last year, I was really nervous about going to Osaka.
I was planning to go to Osaka a lot, but I didn't have a chance to go to Osaka for a while,
But I didn't have a chance to go to Osaka for a while, so I was able to perform in Osaka for the first time in a while. So there were a lot of people who hadn't been to Osaka in a while, and there were also a lot of people who came to Yuzuki's room for the first time.
I asked them how they got to know us. I asked them how they knew me.
90.90%? That's a word you don't hear often.
Ninety-five percent.
No, no, no, a little. Maybe a little less tattoos. Maybe.
Oh, I see. Yeah, I'm very happy.
I was really surprised, and I'm really happy. I'm so grateful.
So, you know, when you are in a rural area, you have to be invisible, otherwise you can't see anything,
But I thought that I could discover a lot when I go there and have a chance to meet people I have never met before,
I would like to perform in various places again. That's great. But there will be more release events in the future, won't there? Yes, I think so.
I think we are about halfway through. Release events. We have just started. How are the reactions to the new song coming along?
The choreography is pretty easy, so they dance along with me. So you are already in it, Tahmin. That's right.
It's not so much an uplifting song, but more of an emotional song...
It's not a song that gets a lot of calls, but people dance to it and listen to it, so a sense of unity is beginning to emerge,
I think this is a song that we will continue to cherish, so I would like to sing it with care,
I think you saw the teaser video of the song.
I think the teaser video was also uploaded, but you can only hear a small part of the teaser.
The one in the kitchen? It's very nice. I can't wait to see it when it comes.
I'm looking forward to it. When can we see it? I'm looking forward to it.
Did she say that? I think so.
You can see it on June 3rd at 9pm!
I'm sure Hairfest is already in full swing, part one and part two.
You can check it out after it's already poofed!
You can see it before the Setoguchi Stater!
Hmmm... that's right.
Can you stop tweeting about how you didn't get selected for the Setoguchi Stater?
I just heard. I'm so sorry.
I asked him how many applications he received, and he said he was selected relatively well.
Can you stop saying that?
It's not that bad... but...
They're doing their best. And they don't take care of the last train.
So people from outlying areas have no choice but to stay in Shinjuku or take a cab to a place where they can stay the night?
That's right.
But he didn't make it.
It's so close, but give me a break!
But I thought you could only participate in the scoring session?
Yes, yes, yes, you don't have to have a ticket for the scoring session.
But it's at 11:30.
You have to be patient until then.
I'm sorry about that.
Well, well, well. You can see it before then.
You can watch it as many times as you want, for about an hour.
I want you to see it.
Very much so, we'll have one too.
We saw the music video earlier in the day, all of us.
It's the first genre I've seen since I became a shirt.
I felt like it was a new genre for me, and I felt nostalgic,
It was both nostalgic and new as a shirt, so there was a freshness to it.
It was a great spectacle,
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing it,
Yes, I think so.
And maybe you'll be wearing the shirt.
The design video is for a song called "Your Trico: Ultimate Love,
I'm playing it at a free live concert right now because it's the perfect song for you.
And then there's a song called Morning Glory and a song called Medal of Honor.
So, actually, there is a medal of honor on the outfit for the awaying beer.
There is something like that, isn't there?
That's the atmosphere of the costume. The design itself.
The fans were saying how cute the medal was.
Actually, there are some small details like the fact that everyone wears a medal from that point of view.
It's really nice, isn't it? Yes, they are very cute.
All four of them look great together. Asha is also very nice. The four of them are so close to each other.
Asha is cute. Yes, she's lovely.
The jacket picture also has a shirt and a bear. Right?
There was one that looked a little bit strong. Like, he's a reader or something.
I think it's becoming more and more obvious.
I don't say much about it. I don't say it's coming to light.
I think it's coming to light.
I really want you to listen to the songs. I've only been able to show people the songs that suit you best, so I'll probably do one more song soon.
So I think you will be able to hear one song at a time again soon, and the number of songs will increase as we go on our free live tour. We are looking forward to seeing you there.
The time for taking pictures at the Lilyway has also gone up.
This week, right?
Didn't he almost attack Mr. Akimoto?
I remember seeing a picture of that.
No, that was part of an attack.
No, you don't admit that until you attacked her.
No, no, no, no. We had a warning about the second part.
I see.
It's good. It's good. It's good.
I don't know what you mean by "it's good".
I don't know what you mean by "it's good." I was just saying that, and then Fotchan was like...
At first he said he would avoid it, but I told him he would look ugly if he did, so he said he shouldn't avoid it.
What kind of advice is that? I said, "Don't do it.
And when I said, "Oh, well, I guess so," he avoided it, so I said, "That's not what I meant by fun.
You seemed to be having a lot of fun.
It was fun. He was very excited, wasn't he?
Yes, Morinami Yaki Zubor itself was having a lot of fun.
We had morning breakfast with Haru and Yoneda before the event started,
We ate a lot of different takoyaki, and we had a lot of fun.
I was in a good mood.I'm glad. We are all happy that Mr. Kobikazu is in a good mood.
And I came home as soon as possible yesterday.
I came home as soon as possible and prepared for the hair festival today.
Oh, how serious. You are busy. What kind of preparations did you do for the hair festival?
I did a lot of preparation today, but I met Amefura.
Amefura? I'm looking forward to meeting you. Like a hello?
I'll leave that to your imagination.
You're not very good at this.
Really?
I met Amefula, and tomorrow I'm meeting Lumaiglo.
Busy week.
I've been preparing for the Hair Fest on Thursday, and after the release yesterday, I've been working on my voice training.
I've been preparing for the hair festival since then, putting in voice training and other things.
So you want me to look forward to it.
Yes, that's right. That's right.
I wonder.
I had a lot of things going on,
It was very fulfilling.
So it was more than a week?
Yes.
That's all for Orca. That's all for Orca.
So that's it for this week. For this week. This week's stop-loss bulletin!
What is this? What's that section? This is the corner where we introduce you to X Girl Dai and Toru Inari who are working locally in Starlast Parallette, of which Shaji is a member. Please help us out.
×Dai x Shoujo and Toru Inari will appear in the first part, and Toru Inari will appear in the second part, separately in the Kosazuki room.
I am very happy to announce that Dai-chan will appear in the first part and Toru Inari will appear in the second part, both in the Kosazuki room,
Tomorrow, she and Rico will be delivering the program together.
Where is the platform?
Stacomic!
You've been doing a lot of collaborations lately, haven't you?
Yes!
I've been working with Yuukka's and Yukirin's. I'm getting more and more invitations.
I've been getting more and more invitations.
Finally!
I'm glad I told you!
It's true!
Liko invited me too.
I'm so glad.
I've been getting scouts and we've been collaborating a lot. That's great.
Tomorrow I'm doing an insta-comic with Rico at 6pm, so please come. Maybe we can talk about how we're a little excited about Yuzuki's hair festival.
I think it would be great to see them talking about how much they're looking forward to it. You mean, "Seeing the two of you enjoying each other's company. That's right. So please watch it. Please do.
What are we going to talk about? I don't know either. I'm not sure either. I'll show you my friend's video 2.
After all, Batten Girl Tai will be performing at the first part of Yuzuki's Hair Fest, and she has some new songs, so I hope you will enjoy her worldview and Vashon-chan's. I hope you will listen to many of her songs,
I would be very happy if you could listen to many of her songs. I hope you will listen to many of her songs. Next, Ginari and Ofuku-chan. Yes, please.
Toofuku-chan, every week we read a message from our leader, Ms. Karin Tachibana, so I would like to read this week's message as well.
Let's see, please wait a moment. Okay.
Here it comes. Here we go. Good evening, Yuzuki-chan, Setoguchi-san, and all my roommates. Good night.
I'm Karin Tachibana from Iginari and Ofuku. I know who you are. This week, I delivered the impressions of the tour and the awarding of the championship for deliberate mockery yesterday.
We heard a lot of behind-the-scenes stories about the tour, and Kalin had a lot of fun. The awards for the "Intentional Mockery" championship were also very interesting, as the works and prizes chosen were very individualistic.
Thank you so much for dancing so many dances at the Deliberate Mockery Championships. I watched all of them. They were all so mocking. Personally, I am looking forward to the second round.
I'm going to go see the hashtag "Deliberately Mocking Championship" every once in a while, so I'd be happy if you guys dance more.
And yesterday was member Norine's birthday. Happy birthday to Rine!
Rine is always so kind and calm, I feel so safe when I'm around her.
Thank you for always being kind to me.
I hope this year will be another wonderful year for you.
I look forward to working with you for a long time to come!
Well, that's all for today. See you soon! Thank you!
So, you went through the tour and did the feedback.
You did, didn't you? We did it on purpose. You don't do it, Hongo-san?
Various people have posted videos saying that there were a lot of them. But Yuko also posted it on her Instagram.
Can you see George like that? George?
Oh, I'm sorry. Always. My interpretation of George was in katakana, right?
Someone like "George is...". It's been hijacked. Daikoku-san's installations.
If George was there. If George's picture was like this.
If there was a picture of George in front of the log house. That's a lot of work, but would you always be able to see it?
I can see it all the time. So I'm just missing it.
But we talked about it.
Oh, did we? Did I?
The one where you're really mad at me.
Awww!
That's terrible!
Did I say that?
Yeah, he was very complimentary.
Look, you didn't think it would stay with me?
It's going to stay.
So look at it.
It's nice.
It's a rare bruise.
Can I do something for you? Now.
What? Why?
Well, I mean... maybe I can't sing, but... But, you know, you'll get to see it.
You don't have to do it today. What do you mean?
What do you mean?
Oh, really? You mean there is? I don't know where it is.
I don't know where you can find it, but I have Tip-san and Orca-sama in the pipeline.
Are we going to talk about the killer whale now? It has nothing to do with Mr. Shachi, does it?
By the way, there may be a pattern to cover. Oh, really?
Various important information is oozing out right now.
Oh, that's right. Well, I'm getting more and more excited.
I'll take a look too. Please do.
I understand. Let's dance together.
Shall we reel it in backstage or something? You mean the place where I'll be, right?
In Yuzuki's room. Normally.
You're so sure about that? I said, "Let's take a TikTok in Yuzuki's room.
Oh, you're going to shoot TikTok in Yuzuki's room? With Mr. Setoguchi.
With who? Yuzuki.
Oh, what? Which one? On which account?
Oh, Mr. Okura... that's not him, is it? Because Mr. Okura...
No, it's not there. That's why you're posting it on Instagram.
Oh, that's what you mean. You can't tell if I say reel.
Hey! Winner! I know what a reel is!
Winning! You can't tell me what a reel is!WIN! You can't tell me it's a reel!
Yes, I got it. Thank you very much.
I know.
I told you it's TikTik.
I said it's TikTik.
Did you say TikTok about reels?
I don't know anything about reels. Is TikTok about reels?
Well, there's a big category called "video". That's not fair. I don't know about that, that's...
Yuzuki also filmed with a reel. Oh, you mean you're going to give it to me.
I've never taken any pictures. Rainbow.
I'm going to solve everything on my own.
I'm like a person who gets into trouble at a family restaurant at 2 a.m.
He asked me if I wanted to do some work.
What is it?
Let's take pictures later.
No, no, no, it was at the festival, wasn't it?
Oh, I even remember the festival.
Wait a minute, Mr. Carpenter has been drinking today.
I've been scared for the last 5 minutes.
What are you talking about?
I understand.
Then let's film.
If something happens, let's film it.
It's a boundary.
It's good, isn't it?
There seems to be a lot going on, so let's hope for the best. I look forward to working with you.
Yes, please.
That's all for this week.
There is more.
I wonder what's in store.
This week's night runner.
Please give my best regards.
This is one of our net regulars, Lulu Luna's
What's going on all of a sudden?
It's Lulu Luna, isn't it?
To Ms. Luna Luna.
This is the section where we look back on a week in the life of Ms. Lunoluna.
Please do.
I have received this week's report, so I will read it.
I'll read it.
Please read it.
Good evening, Yuzuki-chan, set goods, and roommates.
I'm Runa-san from Lulu Lulu, and this week's Nairun.
I'm Runa-san, this week's Nairun, and thanks to Mizuki's room, I was able to make another cute acquaintance at the Stapler, and I'm very happy.
And yesterday we had our first concert in Shibuya, the first time in a long time, but we were nervous and nervous because it was the first time we had a live concert against each other.
I was so excited and nervous, but it ended without a hitch.
I'm looking forward to wearing it a lot in the future.
This Wednesday, May 31st, at midnight, we will start distributing the new song "Sakura Nagashi".
I've been talking about it on the group line of the three members of Lumaiglo, and I'm already thinking that a live show created by three people from different fields would be absolutely fantastic!
I'm looking forward to it!
We will do our best to make Maiglo happy to have Rumpin as a member.
Let's aim for the Yuzuki-chan Summer Festival, too.
We are very happy to be able to perform in the second part of the festival, and we feel that we have become one step above the semi-regulars.
Yuzuki-chan, Mr. Setoguchi, my roommates and I look forward to seeing you at Yuzuki-chan's hair festival.
That's all for this week's Lulu, Luna.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you.
I see. So you are going to showcase the genres of each of the three directions and what you like?
Yes, that's right. I have a rehearsal tomorrow, so if I finish early, it will be when I finish early,
The three of us are talking about the possibility of distributing it.
But I am a geek in every direction.
That might be a hint. I see. Please look forward to it.
I wonder what we're going to do.
You talked about it like it's been decided so much.
You two are really giving me a lot of input, so it was a pretty smooth decision.
It was a pretty smooth decision.
We decided on the parts for each of them.
We were talking about doing it on the day of the event.
It's amazing that they can do that, isn't it?
But they've all been doing this for a long time.
Mai Mai and Rumpin...
I trust them a lot. Tomorrow's rehearsal will be the only one.
The rest will come on the day of the show, so we'll work a little bit harder, and then we'll have a little bit of time to do it.
I'm hoping to have a little bit of time to work on it, and then I'll be able to stream it, so please stay tuned.
I'll start in the evening.
Oh, you might be able to see Mr. Okura on consecutive days, right?
Yes, that's right.
Yes, that's great.
Please look forward to it.
Please do.
Okay, I guess that's all then.
Yes, that's all.
Yes, that's all for this week's series.
[Applause]
So, that's it.
Yes, that's it.
Oh no.
The next project.
This time.
There isn't one.
[laughter]
Unfortunately.
Oh no.
Do you have, uh, anything?
Do you have a place? I have a place!
You want to shoot TikTok now? You want me to film it?
No, not TikTok. The reel.
Oh, she doesn't know what a reel is!
Oh, I see. I see.
Reel, reel, reel. No choice, no choice, no choice.Reel, reel, reel, no choice, no choice, no choice.
Reel, remember, insta-reel.
I'm so pissed! I hate it when you do it with your arms shuffle-shuffle-shuffle!
Remember, it's called "shuffle-shuffle".
Shall we film? I want to take a picture. What do you want to take a picture of?
Well, let's do this Enjoy Life thing together because I want everyone to know...
We should film it.
Let's get Mr. Mizukami in the shot.
Let's film it. Just the four of us.
How do we film this?
How do we film it?
I don't really know either.
What? You were editing Moeike so much?
I don't know much about reels.
What? You didn't use the reel, did you?
I was using a reel, but I don't know how to use a reel.
You mean the original?
Yes, that's it!
Now that you're up on your feet, come on in.
I'll put on some cute filters.
Is that because I'll be in the picture?
I'll put a cute filter on it. That's definitely not the point.
Let's take it off.
I wonder if I'll ever have an enjoyable life, Reel. Oh, there it is!
Wow, I knew it. But, I wonder if it's OK to say "enjoy your life"?
Can't we retrofit it like this, right? Can it be retrofitted?
You can, right? No, how? We'll just play it in our ears?
Yes! In the brain tube!
It's not rusty at all! It's where we use it!
That's not good! That's it!
So you want to try it that way?
I'm in a meeting right now.
Let's take a picture of something totally unrelated, shall we?
It says here that he wants to see the two of you on purpose, on purpose.
On purpose, on purpose?
But what? They're amazing, aren't they?
Isn't it pretty difficult? Are you doing something like this?
This?
Have you done this? Like this?
Have you done this?
When it comes to playing the soundtrack.
I see. Yes, that's right.
What would you like?
Do you watch TikTok? Usually.
I do.
Do you? What do you watch?
It's hard to choose what to watch.
Like videos of rabbits. Animals?
Once I see animals, I see a lot of animals. I also see a lot of animals.
Once I watch a video of a bar crawl, or a video of a delicious meal, that's all I watch.
I can see videos of recommended bars, restaurants with long lines, etc. It's amazing, isn't it?
That system is amazing, isn't it?
Yes, it is. It's great, great, great.
I am also an animal person, or an idol.
I do my own nails.
Is there a video of you doing your own nails?
Like, "Here's how it's done"?
I watch videos of people doing it like that.
I see.
That video is also flowing a lot.
Izumi-san has gone away.
They say the volume doesn't change even if you hold the microphone.
Oh no.
That's really harsh.
No, but Yuzuki's a little bit.
Please come, everyone.
It's really just a few more days.
What about the birthday party?
What about that one?
Mine?
I'm sorry.
Can we talk about me once?
I'm so embarrassed.
If you didn't win a ticket to the birthday party...
You can't see it, right?
Unyah!
What? Unyah?
I love it!
Well, how do you say it?
It's hard to explain.
You all signed up for the priority viewing area, right?
This is the area that's been reserved for you.
The first floor of Mystery Circus itself is entrance-free, right?
Oh, yes, that place is called the venue.
There was a priority viewing area, wasn't there?
Yes, there was a priority viewing area.
It is free, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Well, you can't enter the viewing area, but you can still see the show.
But I think it says that you can't enter any more except for the priority viewing area.
Except for the priority viewing area...
You know, standing around and stuff.
So I have to go through it a bunch of times to get a good look?
I can't say that, though.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What's with that gray area?
That's scary.
Oh, I see.
So, the scoring times are separate from the place.And you don't have to be there for the scoring times.
So those who have not bought tickets can participate in the event if they have purchased at least 3,000 yen at the merchandise store on the first floor of Tokyo Miss Eri Circus that day, even though the event starts at 11:30 p.m.?
Do you think they'll sell T-shirts?
Isn't that a really good design? It was cool, but 53 T-shirts?
What's the number 3? I don't know.
Let's take a picture.
Wait a minute, it's suddenly gone. The reel is gone.
One moment, please.
So... enjoy your life, remember?
Do you remember it? The chorus... I don't know.
Okay.
What should I do?
Oh, I see. I see.
I'm learning now, Mr. Oi.
What?
The reel.
Yes, I'm learning.
I wonder why he looked so smug back then.
Okay, it's done.
Can you do it?
Yes, I'm ready.
You're taking these with a camera?
What?
That's impossible.
Um...
Do it like this and go in the back.
Someone has to hold it.
Yes, sir.
Where are you coming from?
When Ho-chan says, "Here we go.
Enjoy life on a mission.
Yes, sir.
Don't worry, it's going to be a bumpy ride
I think there's going to be a song.
I'll ask you to dance as long as you can remember
Go to the front or go to the front
Let's do "Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, let's do that
How many seconds is this reel?
Thirty seconds long.
I wonder how long 15 seconds is. I wonder how far it goes.
I'll give it a try. Let's make it 15.
Okay, okay. Let's do it.
Is it in? Is it in?
Just about at the shoulder level.
What's with the three of us? We'll never get the word out, will we?
I'm going to make sure it goes viral, I promise!
I'll go to the middle. It's a symbolic image.
That might be good.
What are you getting ready for?
No, it's not starting.
Then I'll throw in three, two, one.
Okay, I'm on it!
I'll push.
I don't know if I can do it.
I don't know.
This isn't going to be a hit.
I told someone, didn't I?
It's never going to go viral.
I'll check it out.
I wonder if any other groups will do it.
Enjoy life!
This is pretty bad.
No, but I've already finished it.
Let's see what we can do with it.
Let's take a look.
Is everything okay?
Then we'll see what happens next.
What's with the three of you?
I'll remember this.
Oh, Mizukami-san!
What's this, Mizukami-san?
He's copying me.
It's okay if he's copying you.
I'll give you this.
Thank you, Ms. Mizukami.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you got a good shot.
It would be nice if everyone could do it.
I want you to do it.
I hope you'll try it, too, and let us know how you did it.
Then we can see that everyone can dance.
Let's choose a cover.
I said, "What do you have?
We have something like this.
Where would you like to go when you leave?
You're right.
I don't have any doubts.
That's for sure.
It's not an enjoyable life at all at the end of the day.
You want to go to Don's or something? That's great.
Setoguchi, you're amazing. No, it's fine.
I'll use this one. I'll give it to you now.
I'll put Yuzuki's Hair Fest announcement on it.
What should we use as a hashtag?
What do you think?
Enjoy Life.
Please let me know if there are any hashtags you would like to add.
What hashtags are popular right now?Like the hashtag that's buzzing right now.
It's bad! That's vicious! Okura-san!
That's too desperate!
It's desperate!
Now that's buzz!
It's got to be a buzz.
Well, well, well. You're right.
He's looking into it. Anything. You can say whatever you want.
Yeah.
Diet.
I don't know though. They might think it's a diet.
What would you put on it, Setoguchi-san?
Hmm?
What would you like to put on it?
What would you like?
What are you wearing?
Enjoy Life Diet
What should I do?
Yuzuki, you only live once.
That's cool.
You only live once?
There can't be that many tomorrows, can there?
Absolutely not.
What do you like?
You're good at that, Mr. 2. It's called a life of convenience.
I like the life of a flight attendant.
Okay, I'll give it to you.
I wish at least one of the members of Orca-san's group would react.
Like this.
I'll give it to you.
I got it.
Yay!
I don't know.
I'd like you guys to play it back a little. I'm counting on you.
Well, I want it to play. Okay, it's up.
Okay, it's up. Okay.
Okay, I'll really keep this in mind. I'll keep this in mind.
So, we can all do this together. I had a good time last year.
It was fun. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Mr. Omuro, I thought so last year, too. You must be really strong.
No, but I sleep like a mud the next day.
But the next day is Shibuya, right?
Yes, so I can't sleep like a mud.
You shouldn't say that idols sleep like mud.
No, they do.
Because you're going to the birthday party too, aren't you? Yes, I will.
You posted it on your Instagram, didn't you?
You know, in your story.
That's a little unfair.
You made a way to escape from the situation.
It's not fair.
Please don't leave me behind.
People are buying our products because you're here.
A little bit is not fair.
I mean, stop that kind of thing.
I can't last an hour and a half by myself.
No, no, no, no.
What are you doing? I don't know anything about it. A birthday party.
What are you going to do? Will they sing? Will they talk?
Will it be a bit like a feedback session?
I'd like to look back on that, too.
What are you doing?
bleep bleep bleep.
I never said I wanted to do a birthday party.
If you're going to stop?
I wonder, are we going to look back on Yuzuki's festival?
Last year, I invited Naito-san and Asu Ogawa to join the festival.
I wonder how it will turn out.
But, you know, he did some kind of dissertation the other day.
Can you do a dinner show when most of the performances are standing?
You can't do a dinner show.
What's it going to be like?
We'll have karaoke.
You are?
We'll have a karaoke machine.
You can sing whatever you want on the spot.
Can you do that?
I don't know. I don't know.
Why did I go and record for the hair festival today?
Is that different? The system?
No, it's not.
That's ridiculous.
I'm going to sing along with YouTube and stuff.
I'll do it at home then. Invite everyone over to the house.
YouTube, hey, why did you put Mr. Water God in your forehead?
Ew. What are we going to do, seriously?
We should prepare another song for the two of us to sing together.
Oh, you'll sing it for us? If I ask you to sing.
I'd be happy to do that.
That would be great.
If your throat is alive.
Please keep it alive. You'll be on the stage the next day, too.
By all means.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're looking forward to it?
I'm sorry about that.
Will there be two shots at the scoring session?
I'd like to see.I'd like to see that.
You don't do a lot of two-shot meetings, do you?
No, I don't.
But I see a lot of two-shot sessions.
Two shots?
I think that's why Lumen-san takes them when he comes over.
He's kind of standing out in the open.
He's standing out front? Is he standing out in the open?
Some of them are just people who came to an escape game.
Or people who come to the escape games.
I see.
I guess so, but...
What do you mean by "out in the open"?
I wonder...
It's 11:30 p.m., right?
But it was basically a birthday party?
How long was the party?
An hour and a half?
An hour and a half.
That's a long time.
It was crazy, really.
But a birthday party?
And watch a sloppy old man who's worked like a horse and buggy eat cake?
In Kabukicho at that time?
Yeah.
What? Are you serious?
We're all together, so sing Happy Birthday.
And whoop it up.
That's the last thing I want to do.
I've been running away from that kind of thing.
And then we'll have our picture taken.
Let's have our picture taken.
Let's make it an OK time to take pictures.
For everyone?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's make some photo okey-dokey time.
Uncle Dan and I will make a cake?
Thank you, guys.
Okay, I'll do the same.
You're a superstar.
That's the kind of thing a superstar should do, but it's my birthday.
You mean the starring role? It's not my birthday.
It's February 14th. Why did I get so many calls from friends?
Why are you doing it on that day?
Does Setoguchi change his birthday on such occasions? he said.
No, it's not like that at all. It's just a bit of fun.
That's funny.
Let's do something.
Yes, please.
Please come.
If you can get tickets, please come.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, please.
Yes, like this? This is the week.
Are we done?
This week...
Is this how it's going to be this week?
This is the last delivery before Yuzuki's hair festival.
Yes, it's an important one.
But I feel like a lot of information came out.
Yes, it is.
It's going to be very exciting, isn't it?
The other members are excited too.
Really?
Yes, they are very excited about Yuzuki's hair festival every year.
Really? I'm so happy.
I'm very happy, and as I always say, it's the right time to release something.
How do you like Yuzuki's hair? I'm grateful for that.
I am grateful for that, but I think the best thing is for the performers to enjoy themselves.
I would be happy if that could be conveyed to the roommates who are watching the show.
I would like to create that atmosphere.
I think I've been able to create a sense of Yuzuki's hair for two years in a row, but I don't know what will happen again this year.
I don't know what will happen again this year, but I hope we can have fun and get together.
Rather.
I'm not sure if I'll be able to do it again this year, but I hope we can have a lot of fun and get together,
So, I'm sure we will have a lot of fun this year.
Did you meet with the students of STAPLA?
Yes, I have met them,
I've met them.
They were back-up dancers for our tour finale,
I also saw her as an opening act when I went to see your wife the other day,
He also comes to our live performances from time to time, and I have had the chance to see him,
I have seen her sing a little bit, but maybe recently she has been doing more and more things.
I think there are a lot of people who are seeing us for the first time because we are all research students,
I hope you will enjoy the opening act.
I would like the audience to come to the venue as soon as possible.
First of all, it's a novelty that the fake father sings at the same time as the audience.
I don't even know who he is singing for.
He is a very good singer. He is very good. I want you to hear it.
I want you to listen to him. He sings with such a great feeling. I like it when he sings "Nise Papa.
I'll tell you this because we had a rehearsal this time, too, but since other people besides me, including Nise Papa and Ogawa-kun, were going to do karaoke, we made a separate group for them.
Nisepa and Ogawa-san were very motivated. I'm glad, though. Really?
What are you going to do? I asked them, "What are you going to do?
I want time to practice this song and that song. What do you mean, practice? When are you going to do it?
You are taking it very seriously.
I hope you can look forward to that emochi.
We have to be as enthusiastic as they are.
Yes, I wonder if we can do that. No, no, no, no, I'm not familiar with your music, to be honest.
Is that so? Genegya?
Hmm?Hmm?
Again? Are you a little tense today because of this?
Mr. Okura, because of this, you're being a little aggressive today. You're really starting a fight with me, aren't you? I'm not selling.
Are you sure? You asked me plainly, now.
No, no, no, I'm not from your generation, but it was a big hit.
I knew the song, but if you ask me if I listened to it a lot, I didn't. But that's exactly what we were doing on that day.
But that's exactly what we did on the day of the concert.
That song.
That's right. I don't like it.
I'm so scared.
I have three hours of voice training, but I'll do it with you.
What? That song?
Various. If you come to Yuzuki's hair festival in Nagoya.
That's the most serious thing I've ever heard. If you say so.
I have to watch Daikoku-san's voice all the way through the unrelated songs? Like this.
I'd say, "That's great.
Do you drink water?
Do I have to say, "Do you drink water?
With a zoom or something.
Am I a remote?
I'm so embarrassed at home.
I have to do that part.
There's a time lag.
I don't know the timing.
I'm way off.
But I really think that the song depends on Mr. Setoguchi.
It's the worst.
Don't you think so? But... No, I don't. I think it would be wonderful to hear Oguro-san's voice singing that song.
I feel sorry for him because I would get in the way. But I chose it because I thought it would be great if Setoguchi-san sang it.
Let's have fun. I understand. Let's have fun. I wonder how much rehearsal time we will have.
We didn't have much time last time. We didn't have time to rehearse, but we didn't have any songs to play together.
I'm sure we won't have any rehearsals. Everyone has their own songs. I hope you will let us sing at least three times.
Three times? We will let them sing three times. Really? Then let's do our best three times.
Fake Papa Setoguchi, Ogawa-san Setoguchi. I don't mind if one of them sings alone.
Then, when you come in, we'll do it backstage and sing a few times.
Where?
ZIP Shinjuku. ZIP Shinjuku. Mr. Shashi?
I'm doing a 20-minute video on MC. It's only 20 minutes.
Twenty minutes? But if we have to sing all the songs in 20 minutes, we won't be able to do it at all, so we will only sing once with a microphone,
So I said, "Let's do it backstage. I don't get to meet most of the performers.
Yuzuki's Airbeth. Is that right? That's right. I'm surrounded by backstage.
I have to meet with my uncles. I see. Yeah, yeah, yeah. If we're going to do it, let's do it.
Let's do it. I'll keep that in mind.
Let's decide. With a bang. Okay. What's this? It says I can do anything in 20 minutes.
I wonder if I can do it. I wonder if it's an MC rehearsal. And is it an MC rehearsal?
Yes, yes. That's what it's supposed to be. So if we have to sing and MC, 20 minutes is tight.
I have never had an MC rehearsal at Yuzuki's Airbes. To be honest.
No. It's really short. It's really short. Talking with the guests.
I don't even know why Setoguchi-san is surrounded by so many people. What? What do you mean?
MCs, you know, until the very last minute of the show, they are very careful with the staff.
I don't do that kind of careful tea ceremony. I don't do that.
So I wondered what they were talking about. No, because there is a script. I have a script, so I have to flow with it.
Time is of the essence, so please keep it tight.
So when I say "wink," he's ready to go.
That's right. That's right.
Thank you very much. I can do it freely.
Last year, you had your own script.
Yes, that's right. I do my best when the guests or performers are present.
Only when the orcas are there, I get lazy.
No, really.
Don't you feel that the three of us at Yuzuki's Hair Fest are really excited?
No, they seemed to be having a lot of fun talking about various things.
I can see that Daikoku-san is in trouble.
I could see that movie.
As for Mr. Shachi, he is used to MCing after the film is over, so he is free to do whatever he wants.
I thought that I and Mr. T would not follow the script.
But when we went there, like the other day, they followed the script exactly when they called for the help of the season.
We were rather surprised.
So, if the script is in the member's jar, they will do it.
You're a big shot!
He's a big name! A big name actor!
Once they're in that jar, they'll practice hard.
That's why you were practicing, right?
They practiced like crazy.
They've been practicing.
They were practicing like crazy.
That's right.
You have a serious side.
If you get into the script this time, you'll do it?
If I get into it, I'll do it, and if not, I'll go free.
I'm scared. I'm scared of not knowing.
I don't know either.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
Everyone is going to be a little bit out there, and it's not like a job, in a good way.
I'm happy that they are doing it that way. Are you happy as a member?
I can only see pictures of me in trouble. I'm in a position to embarrass them.
I was happy to see Daikoku-san's comment during the MC during the live when he saw the three of us knowing about Tricky's lunch box.
I had never seen such a face in Yuzuki's room. I was watching him all the time, in the back.
What? That Daikoku-san is desperately trying to stop them! I thought. I can say it now, but it was very long.
The two of them. It's too long! I thought.
They were moving on to the next one. I think it's good to have members like that.
I thought it would be better to have that kind of atmosphere to show the fun side of Yuzuki's Room.
I'm planning to make this year's festival another one that everyone will be excited about.
Rain is in the forecast, but I hope everyone will come with a good mood and eat delicious food.
We'll be waiting for you. Let's get the word out.
We are now on a free live tour. On June 28th, 4 new songs written by Kenta Matsukuma will be released.
Waiting Bear" will be released on June 28th. We are going on a free live tour with this EP.
There is still half way to go. We will be performing at various venues, and on the day after June 3, we will have a free live concert in Shibuya.
We would be very happy if you could come and join us. We will also be performing a song written by Kenta Matsukuma after the Hair Fest on June 3.I would be very happy if you could come and visit us. Also, after the Hair Fest on June 3, the song that Kenta Matsukuma wrote for us will be released.
I believe that the teaser for the song "Your Prisoner of Ultimate Love" has already been uploaded, and more and more details will be announced.
In addition, there are 4 songs in the album that I think you will really enjoy.
I hope you are looking forward to it.
I hope you are looking forward to it. And on July 9, I will be performing at the Diamond Hall in Aichi Prefecture.
And on July 9th at Diamond Hall in Aichi Prefecture, there will be an orca-produced performance called "Diner Orca".
One part of the show will be a birthday party for Daikoku Shiki, and the second part will be a performance completely produced by the members.
Mr. Daikoku is in charge, isn't he? We're all going to produce it together, but maybe you can listen to what I have to say.
What's your intention, Mr. Daikoku? The live performance itself will be decided by everyone, but I'm sure he'll listen to our requests, for example, if we want our hair to be this way.
For the birthday party, the theme was love, so we decided that calls are ok, so we will prepare songs that include various calls and songs that convey our love to everyone.
We have prepared a lot of songs to express our love to everyone, so if you are a teacher of Yuzuki, Naoshi, Honokaoshi, Haruoshi, or even if you have never seen Shachi, please come and join us.
The second part of the show will be produced by the members.
Now that the ban has been lifted, we would like everyone to speak up and be more vocal.
Cheer up? To cheer them up? I guess.
I hope we can give you a live performance that will cheer you up.
The members of the band will produce the show completely,
I'm sure we'll do a lot of things that are a bit silly,
I'm sure everyone at Roo-mate loves that kind of thing,
I'm sure you guys love that kind of thing, so I hope you can join us and have a good time being silly.
And all this will be held at Nagai Castle on July 22nd.
I'm really looking forward to seeing you all at the Shirtsama on July 22nd at Nagai Castle.
Last year, Shirtsama came back for the first time in a long time.
But it was postponed until October.
We had to postpone the event to October, and we couldn't perform, but it was a very successful and enjoyable event within the limitations of the event,
This time, we will be able to perform in mid-summer, so I think we will be able to show you an even more powerful Shirtsama.
We have already decided on the setlist and other things we want to do,
I am really looking forward to a very spectacular live performance.
I am really looking forward to the show, and I hope that everyone will come to the show with these expectations in mind.
Let's make a lot of noise, dance, and make a fool of ourselves. We are looking forward to seeing you there.
I am sure there will be many other opportunities to see Natsu-Shachi, such as in various other concerts and events, as well as at various festivals.
Natsu-shachi is very vocal,
I feel that Natsu-shachi has become even more powerful since they became able to perform in the "Kabuki" series.
I feel that they have become stronger, so I would like you to experience this strong orca.
Please check social networking sites for more information. We are looking forward to seeing you.
Is that all right?
Let's go to the "Let's ask Mr. Mizukami to tell us about his recommended lectures" corner. Mizukami-san, please.
Yes, I am.
Today, we are going to play the Real Escape Game, and we are going to escape from the bombers along the psychopathic management society.
Okay.
The story is about the Real Escape Game in collaboration with the anime "Psycho-Pass," which is led by the 10th Anniversary Project, and will be held in 6 cities across Japan.
Okay, so the story is about a research student who wants to become a watchdog.
The story is that you are a research student who wants to become a watchdog.
Kinoza, the senior watchdog, and Yellow Hair, the marshal.
And find the bomb that's been planted.
Yes, sir.
In the event...
We'll use the hue scans to track down the culprit.
And decide whether or not to use the dominator.
You can enjoy the same experience as the original.
Hmmm...
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no, no.
Saying "yes" twice is not the end of the story, Mikami-san.
I heard that everyone who participates gets something nice.
That's right.
For all participants.
A clear card with the Dominator's sights on it.
It's cool, isn't it?
I like it.
Psycho-Pass Escape will start the day after tomorrow, Wednesday the 31st.
Become an observer and confront the crimes of a near-future society while immersing yourself in the world of Psycho-Pass.
This show will be held at Tokyo Mysteries Academy!
It starts this Wednesday, and the first weekend falls on Yuzuki's complicated.
And we're going to have a birthday party at Tokyo Mysteries Circus.
It's a very busy time of the year.
That's right.
So the schedule of Tokyo Miceli Circus employees is
Psychopath, I would like your schedule to be on Cicada's birthday.
Mystery schedule!
Too much paiyso, hey!
Please, please buy them all kinds of goods and stuff!
Please, please, please!
We're doing a lot of shows.
I'll tweet the schedule later.
Goods
If there's anything you're interested in, please play with it.
I hope you'll enjoy it.
We have a lot of goods.
We have a lot of goods, so please buy some of them.
I'm so sorry.
Yes, you're right.
That's okay.
I would be very happy if you would just buy them.
And there's one more thing I'd like you to introduce, Ms. Mizutani.
One more thing.
A story about experiencing Tokyo Dome City, which will be scrapped.
It will be the magical place of twilight amusement park!
Yes, this is the one we've introduced before, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
I'll say it again.
Please say it again.
It takes place in an amusement park at twilight and
Kiito.
Yes, sir.
This is where you are free to move about
by what you see, hear, and talk about.
It is a new storytelling experience where the story changesIt's a new storytelling experience where the story changes!
Oh, to all of those performers.
So the story changes when you talk to the people who play the roles?
Yes, sir.
Uh-huh.
And this is it.
What is Magic Place Amusement Park?
The Magic Place Amusement Park is...
It is a magical amusement park that appears quietly at twilight.
You can reach it by riding on a secret playground equipment.
It's a fantasy.
It is said that when you visit this place, you'll forget one bad memory and feel like you're in a dream.
One day, you received an invitation.
I'll be waiting for you at the Horoba Amusement Park in the twilight hours.
What have all these people forgotten, and what do you think they've forgotten here at the Horoba Amusement Park?
Yes, the amusement park at twilight is the setting for your own experience of the mysterious.
Your timing of coughing is too strange.
It hasn't changed, and the barking has cleared my throat.
Stop making edits to the "Twilight of the Dusk" and start streaming it live!
A magical story set in an amusement park at twilight time that you yourself will experience is about to begin!
This is a very limited run, only one weekend a month!
Please get your tickets as soon as possible!
The show starts this weekend, June 2nd at Tokyo Dome Scene!
We look forward to seeing you there!
Thank you very much.
You haven't mentioned this yet, Mr. Mizukami?
No, actually.
I participated in the debugging. It was a kind of guest performance.
How was it?
Well, we did a lot of walking in the Tokyo Dome Shoe.
So, the amusement park is still there, but it's a little more like a Mafrova amusement park, and it has a more solid worldview.
That's right. The first thing we did was to ride the attractions.
Oh, so you actually ride the attractions.
Yes, we do. The first ride.
And then we go into the Holover Amusement Park. I see.
So it's a system that allows you to enter into the story quickly and easily. Yes, it is.
I see. This is also limited to one month, so please join us.
So, this was the "Let's learn from Mr. Mizukami, the scrapper" corner.
There is only one more thing. What?
Yes, I think there will probably be a Setoguchi Birthday Festival this weekend,
I've brought some recommendations for goods you should buy there.
Hmmm.
This one is called "Message Bottle,
It's so small.
I introduced it here before, but this is the actual package.
It's the one you can do at home, where the story starts from the bottle.
This is an escape game.
In the story, you are the main character who finds this bottle on the beach.
It's like going through the story, but it's really like this on the inside.
Wow, it's so stylish!
There is something that says, "Yes.
It's a recommendation.
Yes, this is it.
The price is 2980 yen.
That's not fair!
Yes...
I almost got cheated!
You can't have just one!
2,980 yen!
That's over 3000 yen!
I'm just in time to get in on the scoring.
I'm on the edge.
You just introduced a last-minute cheat.
Hey!
Are you sure you're recommending this?
It's not just the packaging.
I hear it's a lot of fun.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your time.
So, Mr. Ogura, yesterday was the last time we had a talk before the festival. How was it?
It was a lot of fun. By the way, I received a comment from a member on the reel.
I'm very happy.
Two of them.
That's great.
First of all, Haruna-san.
Thank you, Haruna-san.
It's a mega heart emoji.
Thank you very much. I'm very happy.
Honoka-san.
I became a fan.
It's done!
You're buzzing, aren't you?
You must have a fan.
It's like they've become my guess.
I'm so happy.
I got a lot of comments,
Please take a look at it, later.
Please, there are many warm comments,
I think it will give you courage.
I think you will want to do the Setoguchi Eight Group.
No, no, no, I don't not want to do it.
So you mean you might do it only in the front.
I see.
It was fun.
I didn't even have to smell anything.
I think there were glimpses of important information,
I think there were some important information that came out,
I think that was the point.Like, was it that thing?
Yes, it might be.
It's important.
Tomorrow at the Lou Maiglo,
I'm still undecided,
I'm hoping to be able to distribute it,
I hope you can watch it,
Lumaiglo,
If you watch the video, you may be able to get a better idea of what to expect from us,
I hope you will check it out and look forward to it.
Is that all? I see. So, now that that's all said and done, let's get to the Yuzu Hinaya Festival,
Yuzu Hinaya Fest is coming up this weekend, Saturday, September 3, at Zep Shinjuku, and there are only a few tickets left for the first and second parts.
I've said a lot of things today during this broadcast, including some hints,
I would like to ask you to spread the word as much as you can.
Let's end with a few words of enthusiasm. Mr. Oguro. I'm counting on you.
Oh, I see. Samnee. Thumbnail.
Oh, you have one check. Who is it?
We received a room name from a super big eco-friendly person. Thank you very much. Always. Here it is.
Jeez! This time, right?
With Momochan, with Momochan, with Momochan, with Momochan... Oh, Rouman and Momochan. Wrong.
I went this way, and it was this way. Because of the mirror. Is it so hard to recognize them on the monitor now?
You're Luman and Momoa-chan, aren't you? Thank you for writing this. Thank you very much.
The clothes, the outfit. The touch of the picture is a little different from usual.
It's Eiko's thumbnail. The dice are very good.
Very good. I wonder how he writes this. It's amazing.
He is really good. The back also has a pattern of Yuzuki's room, Yuzuki's room.
Oh, that's right. You really paid attention to every detail.
Thank you very much. Thank you, Eiko.
The color of the thumbnails is changing more and more, so I would like you all to check it out,
If you have any good ideas for thumbnails, please send them to me.
If you have any good ideas for thumbnails, please send them to me. Please send your ideas to the address in the summary section. Please send them to scrapmagazine.com. Please send it to scrapmagazine.com. Thank you very much. Let's welcome June 3rd with a word of encouragement.
I guess this is the third year in a row that the festival will be held. I'm really happy to be able to do it for the third time, partly because of the timing of the 200th anniversary.
I'm really grateful for the support from all of my lumemates.
I am very grateful for the support I have received from all of my lumemates.
I'm also very happy to know that there are only a few tickets left for Yuzuki's hair festival,
I also want to see the words "Soul Doubt" for every minute or two,
I hope we can make this event a complete success,
I would like to do my best to make this a great success so that we can do it again in the fourth year,
I am sure that we will be able to witness the history again,
Please look forward to it.
Let's all do our best! Let's do it again!
That's good. I think it's simple and good.
It's the first yuzuki hair festival where you can speak out,
What is it like?
I'd like to hear many people's voices,
I'd like to hear a lot of your voices, and I think it will be a different kind of hair festival from the past Yuzuki hair festivals,
Let's have fun!
See you at Yuzuki's Hair Fest!
We are looking forward to seeing you this Saturday!
Good night!
Hmmm...
Hmm...
Mmm
mmm
Hm
[ED
undefined